Guide to the Brooklyn location scouting photographs collection CBHM.0017
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 19: Downtown Brooklyn, 1992-2010
  - Brooklyn Family and Supreme Court [360 Adams Street], 2010 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Series 20: DUMBO, circa 1988 - 2011
  Series 20: DUMBO includes photographs of areas under the Brooklyn and Manhattan Bridges, apartments, manufacturing and industrial warehouses, offices, parks, bars and restaurants, gyms, stores, and streets in the DUMBO neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - Under the Brooklyn Bridge [DUMBO], circa 1988 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    This folder includes photographs of York Street and Pearl Street, Main Street and Water Street, Front Street, Washington Street, Adams Street, Cadman Plaza East, Prospect Street, Collumbia Heights and Vine Street, Old Fulton, Dock Street.
  - Under the Brooklyn Bridge, circa 1988 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    This folder includes photographs of Front Street, York Street, Adams Street, Pearl Street, Water Street and Anchorage Place, Plymouth Street, Washington Street.
  - Under the Brooklyn Bridge, around the Manhattan Bridge, circa 1988 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    This folder includes photographs of Front Street and Adams Street, Front Street and Pearl Street, York Street and Pearl Street, La Playa de Ponce, Water Street and Jay Street, Anchorage Place and Water Street, plymouth Street at Anchorage Place.
  - 8 [Old] Fulton Street, explosion POV, circa 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - [DUMBO], circa 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - EXT Warehouse area, under Manhattan Bridge, under Brooklyn Bridge, circa 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - EXT Warehouse area, Plymouth Street and Washington Street, circa 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - EXT Eastchester apartment, 177 Water Street (Pearl Street and Jay Street), DUMBO, circa 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - DUMBO - loose photographs, circa 1990 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    These photographs depict Front Street and Pearl Street, Manhattan Lights at 155 Water Street, Anchorage Place and Water Street, and Pearl Street and Water Street.
  - EXT Riverbank Settlement, New Dock Street (under Brooklyn Bridge), circa 1990 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - DUMBO: Lot under Manhattan Bridge, circa 1990 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Mona's Space, One Hot Spot, 1 Front Street, circa 1990 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - EXT Construction site, 4 Water Street, circa 1990 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - EXT Construction site, 1640 63rd Street, circa 1990 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - INT Ferrari Staging Area, Front Street and Adams Street, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    This location was scouted for Scent of a Woman.
  - The Brooklyn Loft, 70 Washington Street (between Front Street and York Street), 1991 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - DUMBO, Warehouse Area (under the Manhattan Bridge), 1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    This location was scouted for "Scent of a Woman."
  - INT Ferrari staging area, 18 Fulton service station, Texaco, at Old Fulton Street and Everit Street, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - INT Ferrari staging area, Manhattan Milling and Drying Company, 38 Water Street, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Ferrari staging area, Brooklyn Warehouse Driving, Chambers Paper Fibre Corporation, 139 Plymouth Street at Anchorage Place, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    This location was scouted for Scent of a Woman. This folder was categorized under "Industrial Parks."
  - Vacant lofts, Chambers Paper Fibres Corporation, 139 Plymouth Street, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - 20-40 Jay Street, 11th Floor, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - INT/EXT Pier Warehouse, Pier 1, Fulton Terminal, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - 8 Fulton Street explosion POV, circa 1995 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Holding/catering space, Brooklyn warehouse area, Studio Akiva, 31 Washington Street (between Water Street and Plymouth Street), circa 1995 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - EXT Construction Site, 30 Washington Street, corner of Plymouth Street, circa 1995 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Manhattan Bridge, circa 1995 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - DUMBO miscellaneous, circa 1995 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Gleason's Boxing Gym, 75 Front Street at Main Street, circa 1995 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Main Street pier, circa 1995 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Blow Up: Pearl Street between Prospect Street and Front Street, circa 1995 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Fulton Ferry Esplanade under the Brooklyn Bridge, end of Water Street, circa 1995 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - [DUMBO], circa 1995 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    This folder contains photographs of Adams Street.
  - INT Boxing club, Gleason's Gym, 75 Front Street, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Kate Wollman Ice Skating Rink, Prospect Park, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, Brooklyn Bridge - Brooklyn side, Cadman Plaza West at Fulton Landing, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - EXT Limo and Fifi, New Dock Street between Water Street and the East River, Brooklyn Bridge Esplanade, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Pete's Downtown: 1 Old Fulton Street, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Bridge, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - INT Matt's Bathroom, 110 Bridge Street, 4th Floor, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Blow Up: Adams Street between Prospect Street and Front Street, circa 1998 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - EXT Streetm Manhattan Bridge View, John Street, DUMBO, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - EXT Empire - Fulton Ferry State Park, DUMBO, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - DUMBO Sunset, Manhattan Bridge, Brooklyn Bridge, circa 2000 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    This folder was categorized under "Parks."
  - EXT Construction Site, 10 Jay Street, circa 2000 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Fulton Ferry, circa 2000 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Manhattan Bridge, orange scaffolding, circa 2000 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - EXT Construction Site, State Park and Recreation, 137 Water Street, circa 2000 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - DUMBO miscellaneous streets, circa 2000 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Fulton Ferry State Park, between Brooklyn Bridge and Manhattan Bridge [Empire Fulton Ferry, Brooklyn Bridge Park], circa 2000 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Rooftop, 1 Old Fulton Street, circa 2000 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Garage blow-up: Chambers Paper Fibres Corporation, 139 Plymouth Street at Anchorage Place, circa 2000 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - EXT Streets, Brooklyn, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    This folder includes photographs of Adams Street and Water Street, Water Street and Anchorage Place, Front Street and Pearl Street, York Street and Washington Street, Plymouth Street between Washington Street and Main Street, New Dock Street at Water Street, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, Furman Street and Montague Street.
  - INT/EXT Bar, Between the Bridges Pub, 63 York Street at Adams Street, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - EXT Lot, Con Edison Lot, Pearl Street at John Street, DUMBO, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - [Department of Environmental Protection] DEP lot, Adams Street at Plymouth Street and John Street, DUMBO, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Bliss Spa offices, 50 Washington Street, DUMBO, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn rooftop, 70 Washington Street (between Water Street and Front Street), 2002 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn rooftop, 21 Front Street (between Main Street and Dock Street), 2002 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - EXT rooftop, 70 Washington Street at Main Street (DUNBO), 2002 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Bridge, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Under Brooklyn Bridge, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - EXT Lot, 261 Water Street between Gold Street and Bridge Street, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - INT/EXT Restaurant, The River Café, Old Fulton Street, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Under Brooklyn Bridge, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Manhattan Bridge walkway, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - EXT Park, Brooklyn Bridge Park, Plymouth Street (between Main Street and Washington Street), DUMBO, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - EXT Ash's Apartment, 70 Washington Street / 35 York Street, DUMBO, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - INT/EXT Restaurant and Alley - Rice, 81 Washington Street (between York Street and Front Street), DUMBO, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Plymouth Street at Adams Street, DUMBO, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - INT/EXT Parking Garage, Impark, 66 Front St at Main St, DUMBO, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - EXT Loft steps / INT step hallway, 57 Jay Street (between Front Street and Water Street), 2003 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Pearl Street and York Street, DUMBO, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - EXT Streets/Alleys, DUMBO, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    This folder includes photographs of Pearl Street and Anchorage Place, Adams Street and Water Street, Adams Street and Plymouth Street, Plymouth Street and Pearl Street, Plymouth Street and Jay Street, Bridge Street.
  - Loft steps exterior/interior, 65 Pearl Street at Front Street (between Front Street and Water Street), DUMBO, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn Bridge walkway, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - EXT Ash Crashes into Agent's Car, DUMBO, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    This location was scouted for The Forgotten. This folder includes photographs of Prospect Street and Pearl Street, York Street and Pearl Street, and Anchorage Place.
  - DUMBO and Vinegar Hill, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - INT/EXT Paper Recycling Plant, Chambers Paper Fibers, 139 Plymouth Street at Pearl Street, DUMBO, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - EXT Park, Empire Fulton Ferry State Park, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - EXT Loft, Plymouth Street at Jay Street, DUMBO, circa 2005 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - EXT Park, Empire Fulton Ferry State Park, circa 2005 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - EXT Empire Park, DUMBO, circa 2005 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Fulton Ferry State Park, between Brooklyn Bridge and Manhattan Bridge, circa 2005 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Superfine [Bar, 126 Front Street], circa 2005 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Trent's office, Brookwood Child Care, 25 Washington Street, circa 2005 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - EXT Ash apartment (Alt.) [Gair Building, 83 Front Street], circa 2005 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Fulton Ferry Landing [Pete's Downtown], circa 2005 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - EXT Fulton Ferry Landing, circa 2005 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - The River Cafe, circa 2005 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Powerhouse Arena, bookstore, 37 Main Street, DUMBO, circa 2005 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - INT/EXT Café, The River Cafe, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - EXT/INT Brooklyn Loft, 201 Water Street at Jay Street (51 Jay Street), 2006 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - EXT Waterfront, Fulton Ferry Landing, Old Fulton Street at the East River, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - EXT Manhattan Reveal, Manhattan Bridge from pedestrian walkway, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - INT Gymnasium, Smack Mellon, 92 Plymouth Street at Washington Street, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - EXT NYPD Tow Pound, Vacant Con Edison Lot in DUMBO, John Street between Pearl Street and Adams Street, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - INT Horvath's, 84 Front Street, Apt. 12B, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    This location was scouted for The Sorceror's Apprentice.
  - Vacant office, DUMBO, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    This folder includes photographs of the interior of 191 Plymouth Street or 195 Plymouth Street. 195 Plymouth Street was Dennis Oppenheim's studio at the time.
  - Vacant Office, DUMBO [56 Pearl Street, Pearl Street and Water Street], circa 2010 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - EXT Aaron Black, 10 Jay Street at John Street, circa 2010 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Purified Lofts, 135 Plymouth Street, Loft 204, DUMBO, circa 2010 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - DUMBO, Smack Mellon, Gallery, 92 Plymouth Street, circa 2010 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - INT Apartment, 135 Plymouth Street, Apartment 4B, circa 2010 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - INT Apartment, 135 Plymouth Street, Apartment 407, circa 2010 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - INT Apartment, 135 Plymouth Street, Apartment 209, circa 2010 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - INT Apartment, 135 Plymouth Street, Apartment 4A, circa 2010 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - DUMBO warehouse, 202 Plymouth Street, circa 2010 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - DUMBO, Record Store, Halcyon Records, 45 Washington Street, circa 2010 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Old Man Black (Hearding Aid), 8 Everit Street, DUMBO, circa 2010 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    This location was scouted for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close
  - DUMBO loft, 31 Washington Street, Apt. 13, circa 2010 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - DUMBO event space, 155 Water Street, circa 2010 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - INT Machine Shop, 215 Plymouth Street, DUMBO, circa 2010 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - INT DUMBO Loft, 110 Bridge Street at York Street, 4th Floor, Apartment 1, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - INT DUMBO Loft, 110 Bridge Street at York Street, 4th Floor, Apartment 3 and 2, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - 20 Jay Street (between John Street and Plymouth Street), 2011 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- Series 21: Dyker Heights, circa 1990 - circa 2010
  Series 21: Dyker Heights includes photographs of restaurants, the Brooklyn VA Medical Center, Poly Prep Country Day School, and Bay Ridge Rod and Gun Club in the Dyker Heights neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - INT Hospital, Brooklyn VA Hospital, 800 Poly Place, circa 1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Veterans Administration Hospital, 800 Poly Place at 7th Avenue, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Poly Prep Country Day School, 92nd Street and 7th Avenue, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Hospital, Brooklyn VA Medical Center, 800 Poly Place, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - INT Pistol Range, Bay Ridge Rod and Gun Club, 6718 Fort Hamilton Parkway, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - INT Indoor Pistol Range, 6716 Fort Hamilton Parkway, Bay Ridge Rod and Gun Club, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Poly Prep [Country Day School], 9216 7th Avenue at 92nd street, Dyker Heights, 2000 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - EXT Petrina Diner: 18th Avenue at 85th Street, Dyker Heights, circa 2010 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - EXT New Dyker Restaurant: 85th Street and 18th Avenue, Dyker Heights, circa 2010 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Series 22: East Flatbush, 2001-2004
  Series 22: East Flatbush includes photographs of parks, restaurants, and the Kingsboro Psychiatric Center in the East Flatbush neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - Kingsboro Psychiatric Center and Mary Brooks Hospital, 681 Clarkson Avenue, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Tropical Paradise Restaurant, 1250 Utica Avenue, corner of Avenue D, circa 2000 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Paerdegat Park, Foster Avenue at Albany Avenue, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Jacob Joffe Fields, Avenue K at East 58th Street, East Flatbush, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Mike's Diner, 630 Utica Avenue, corner of Winthrop Street, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Series 23: East New York, 1997-2006
  Series 23: East New York includes photographs of public housing, an industrial dry cleaner, restaurants, and streets in the East New York neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - INT/EXT Industrial Dry Cleaner, Majestic Cleaners, 740 Pine Street, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Housing Project, Boulevard Houses, Stanley Avenue (between Ashford Street and Schenck Avenue), New Lots, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Brothers Deli and Restaurant, 1764 Pitkin Avenue corner of Watkins Avenue, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - EXT Intersection, Miller Avenue at Liberty Avenue, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Housing Project, Cypress Hills Housing, Linden Boulevard and Euclid Avenue, East New York, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Street with Elevated Train, Atlantic Avenue and East New York Avenue, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - EXT Housing Development, Atlantic Avenue at Atkins Avenue, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Series 24: Flatbush, circa 1988 - 2011
  Series 24: Flatbush includes photographs of houses, apartments, Brooklyn College, clubs, churches, a bowling alley, a roller skating rink, and streets in the Flatbush neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - Manhattan EXT, Kings Theatre, 1027 Flatbush Avenue, circa 1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 164 Westminster Road, circa 1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 314 East 16th Street, circa 1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - EXT Movie theater, Astor Theater, 925 Flatbush Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Empire Roller Disco, 200 Empire Boulevard, circa 1990 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Diplomat Lanes 26 Snyder Avenue between Flatbush Avenue and Bedford Avenue, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - INT Amanda apartment, 2124 Albermarle Terrace (off East 21st Street), circa 1995 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Empty lot, Dorchester Road (between Argyle Road and Rugby Road), circa 1995 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - EXT Suburban Street: Argyle Road, Westminster Road, and Albermarle Road and Westminster Road, circa 1995 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Mamma Lucia's [1701 Foster Avenue], 1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    This folder was categorized under "Bars/Nightclubs."
  - EXT Movie Theater, Kings Theatre, Flatbush Avenue, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Ray's House, 1423 Albemarle Road at Marlborough Road, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    This location was scouted for The Funeral.
  - Ray's House, 182 Westminster Road, between Albemarle Road and Beverley Road, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - EXT Movie theater, Kenmore, 2101 Church Avenue, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - INT Melissa's House: 10-01 Ditmas Avenue, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - EXT Street, East 18th Street between Foster Avenue and Glenwood Road, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - INT Sheriff's apartment, 1102 Dorchester Road (between Stratford Road and Westminster Road), 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    This location was scouted for Return to Paradise. This folder was categorized under "Apartments/Lofts."
  - INT/EXT Brooklyn College, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - EXT Harvard, Brooklyn College, 2900 Bedford Avenue, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - EXT College campus / INT lecture room, Brooklyn College, 2900 Bedford Avenue, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - INT/EXT Dad's Older Home, 291 Argyle Road (between Beverley Road and Cortelyou Road), 2003 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Amersfort Park, Avenue I at 40th Street, Flatbush, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - INT/EXT Dad's Older Home, 259 Stratford Road at Matthews Court, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Brooklyn College, The City University of New York, 2900 Bedford Avenue, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - INT Soul Bros, The Jamaican Ex-Police Association, 968 Rogers Avenue between Beverley Road and Tilden Avenue, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - EXT Street, Argyle Road at Albemarle Road, circa 2005 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Salem Missionary Baptist Church, 305 East 21st Street (between Albemarle Road and Regent Place), 2007 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - INT St. Mark's United Methodist Church, 2017 Beverley Road (between Ocean Avenue and East 21st Street), 2007 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - EXT School, Faith Assembly of God, Bedford Avenue at Martense Street, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - INT Ada's, 1305 Albemarle Road between Rugby Road and Argyle Road, Ditmas Park [Flatbush], circa 2010 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Brooklyn College, The City University of New York, 2900 Bedford Avenue, circa 2010 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - EXT Apartment Building, 416 Ocean Avenue at Caton Avenue, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Brooklyn College, Old Gym (3rd floor), 2900 Bedford Avenue, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT House, 322 Argyle Road, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - INT/EXT House, 226 Argyle Road, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - INT/EXT House, 300 Rugby Road, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT House, 1203 Albemarle Road at Westminster Road, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    This location was categorized under "Brooklyn Houses."
  - INT/EXT House, 171 Marlborough Road, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - INT/EXT House, 296 Rugby Road, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT House, 155 Argyle Road, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - INT/EXT House, 472 Argyle Road, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - INT/EXT House, 155 Stratford Road, 2011 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Prospect Lefferts Gardens, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    This folder includes photographs of Maple Street, Lefferts Avenue, Bedford Avenue, and Lincoln Road.
  - EXT "9 Story" Building, 630 Ocean Avenue at Albemarle Road, 2011 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Series 25: Fort Greene, circa 1990 - 2011
  Series 25: Fort Greene includes photographs of apartments, schools, houses, Fort Greene Park, public housing, subway stations, churches, restaurants, schools, and stores in the Fort Greene neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - Tuxedo Shop, Buy-a-Tux, 681 Fulton Street, circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - EXT Construction site, 129 Carlton Avenue (between Myrtle Avenue and Park Avenue), Fort Greene, circa 1990 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - INT Sweatshop, The Door Store, 1 Carlton Avenue, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - EXT Construction Site: Atlantic Avenue and South Elliott Place and Hudson Avenue and Dekalb Avenue, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - EXT Laurel's Apartment: Carlton Avenue between Dekalb Avenue and Willoughby Avenue, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - EXT Laurel's apartment, Adelphi Street between Lafayette Avenue and Greene Avenue, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    This location was scouted for The Associate. This folder was categorized under "Apartments/lofts."
  - "Roach Garden," Fort Greene Park, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Restaurant: 211 Dekalb Avenue (at Adelphi Street), Fort Greene, circa 1995 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - INT Wiggins (or other), 152 Dekalb Avenue (between South Oxford Street and South Portland Avenue), 1996 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - INT Sheriff's apartment, 159 Willoughby Avenue at Hall Street, Apt. 1A, Fort Greene, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - INT Office/Hallway: Blue Stone Partners, Ltd., between Ashland Place and Rockwell Place, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - EXT Gas Station, Fulton Street between Ashland Place and St. Felix Street, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - EXT High school, Bishop Loughlin High School, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Fort Greene monument from roof [Prison Ship Martyrs' Monument], circa 2000 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - INT Brownstone [129 Willoughby Avenue, Clinton Hill], circa 2000 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - INT Amanda apartment, 11 South Elliott Place, Fort Greene, circa 2000 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - EXT Prior's apartment, 304 Carlton Avenue (between Greene Avenue and Dekalb Avenue), 2002 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - EXT Prior's apartment, 300 Carlton Avenue (between Greene Avenue and Dekalb Avenue), 2002 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - EXT Prior's apartment, 298 Carlton Avenue (between Greene Avenue and Dekalb Avenue), 2002 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - EXT Prior's apartment, 259 Carlton Avenue at Dekalb Avenue, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - EXT Prior's apartment, 195 Carlton Avenue at Willoughby Avenue, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - INT/EXT Restaurant, A Table, corner of Lafayette Avenue and Adelphi Street, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Fort Green Park, southeast corner, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Fort Greene Neighborhoods, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    This folder includes photographs of Clinton Avenue and Willoughby Street looking toward Fort Greene Park.
  - EXT Rooftop, Fort Greene, Brooklyn Medical Center, 121 Dekalb Avenue and 240 Willoughby Street, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - INT Townhouse, 138 Lafayette Avenue, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Albert Parham Playground, Clermont Avenue (Dekalb Avenue and Willoughby Avenue), Fort Greene, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - INT Brownstone, 200 Adelphi Street, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - EXT/INT Brownstone, 259 Clermont Avenue (between Dekalb Avenue and Willoughby Avenue), 2003 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Fort Greene Park, Fort Greene, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - EXT Rooftop, Fort Greene, Kingsview Homes, 125 Ashland Street (between Willoughby Street and Myrtle Avenue) and 130 St. Edwards Street, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Williamsburg Savings Bank (HSBC), View from tower, 1 Hanson Place at Flatbush Avenue, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - 58 South Portland Avenue between Dekalb Avenue and Layafette Avenue, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - 36 South Portland Avenue between Dekalb Avenue and Lafayette Avenue, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Housing Project, Walt Whitman Houses, Myrtle Avenue and North Portland Avenue, Fort Greene, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - EXT Townhouse, 199 Carlton Avenue at Willoughby Avenue, 2004 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - INT Apartment, EXT Brownstone, 61 South Portland Avenue between Dekalb Avenue and Lafayette Avenue, 2nd floor, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 11)